[Music]
did you see the autumn trees against the
pale blue sky
[Music]
like two lovers ashen limbs like two
burning sighs stripped of every pretense
in the truth but did you see the autumn
trees fragile beyond repair
did you see
under the sky of
leading into one another
to whisper words of love forever to be
bound they say one heart one
breasts and then to look the other way
and fall down on cold hard cement
so
[Music]
so changeup
you are
[Music]
you are the
and
and the word
[Music]
to just see
the Papi's sway in late summer be
fields of iris and the police the
brightness of hi
the opulence the Ocean Spray the
fullness of
[Music]
to ashes twisted limbs did care
Oh Smarties
in gold
the dark season to come dressed 10,000
shades of gray
monuments of stone like did you see her
standing
broken and
face mysterious air a church with the
house
[Music]
you are so
so change
you are
[Music]
you
you are
[Music]
and
[Applause]
[Music]